LESLEY SABLATURA

11301 JOLLYVILLE ROAD #H2 AUSTIN, TX 78759 · (713) 855-3057 · LESLEYSAB210@GMAIL.COM

SUMMARY

Experienced product manager and product owner with 4 years' experience working with agile software development teams. Collaborative team player with the ability to effectively communicate at all organizational levels. Exceptional problem solving skills, strong business judgement, and demonstrated experience leading the cross-functional development of software products. Certified Scrum Master and Certified Scrum Product Owner who understands the value of good process and the power of continuous inspection and adaptation.

CORE SKILLS & COMPETENCIES

- Project management
- Process improvement
- Product management
- Product design

- User research and insights
- Product strategy
- Data visualization
- Instructional design and training

WORK EXPERIENCE

TAVHEALTH Austin, TX PRODUCT MANAGER 2016-present

- Led design and launch efforts for the latest version of the TAVConnect enterprise product: a collaboration platform that works to help users identify non-clinical information about a patient in order to improve healthcare outcomes. Feature launches of note include: embedded analytics, advanced export, and enhanced usability features.
- Defined and evangelized the product vision, strategy, positioning, requirements, roadmap, and launch plan for TAVConnect and aligned product plans and launch schedules with other properties across TAVHealth.
- Collaborated with Engineering and Operations teams to improve release process, creating more transparency to company and users; and increased response time to production incidences.
- Monitored product metrics after re-launch to ensure product growth and to further refine product features.
- Conducted field user research through in-person and virtual research sessions and translated those market insights into feature changes to improve product engagement and conversion, increasing the leadership position in the enterprise healthcare market.

BUZZ POINTS Austin, TX PRODUCT MANAGER 2015-2016

- Worked with software development, marketing, and related product management teams to innovate on ways to improve customer acquisition and product retention rates. Gauged health of the product, monitored quarter-over-quarter, and created plans to improve overall product health.
- Created a product strategy and roadmap across three of Buzz Points' financial reward program products. Worked with business and tech teams to balance new product development, revenue growth, architectural improvements, and execution on the vision.
- Translated customer needs into business and product requirements. Launched new product called Buzz Insights by using customer insights, hard data, and metrics to drive product development, oversee sprint planning, measure the velocity, set the deployment vision, develop the launch strategy, and successfully deploy beta product.

MCKESSON The Woodlands, TX PRODUCT OWNER 2008-2015

Previous roles: PHYSICIAN PRACTICE MANAGER & SENIOR PHYSICIAN LIASION

- Participated in and led daily scrums, sprint planning meetings, sprint reviews, and retrospectives. Represented the voice of McKesson's broad customer base to all other stakeholders.
- Used SAP Business Objects to build data visualization capabilities for an analytics platform designed for physician liaisons.
 Designed the product visualization and drove the product roadmap to help scale the business at the physician, practice, and network levels.
- Defined and prioritized user stories, triaged bugs, and managed the product backlog. Prioritized the sequences of the backlog
 according to business value and ROI. Logged user stories and software bugs.

SALIX PHARMACEUTICALS

SALES REPRESENTATIVE

Dallas, TX
2007-2008

• Sold four gastroenterology products by prospecting, penetrating, and creating new relationships with clients.

• Delivered the highest level of sales and customer service on behalf of Salix through sales presentations, marketing materials, and sales techniques.

BAYER HEALTHCARE San Antonio, TX DIABETES SALES SPECIALIST 2004-2007

Previous role: RETAIL SALES REPRESENTATIVE

- Promoted Bayer's premiere line of diabetes products and drove deals to closure with hospital systems, physicians, and retail
 pharmacists.
- Utilized CRM tools to track all pertinent account information and sales progress.
- Ranked #3 in the nation out of 175 Diabetes Sales Specialists in 2006-2007 fiscal year.
- Ranked #1 in the nation out of 40 Retail Sales Specialists in 2005.

EDUCATION & TRAINING

AUSTIN CODING ACADEMY
Full Stack Software Engineering Certification
2018

MBA, TEXAS WOMAN'S UNIVERSITY

Business Administration & Management 2013

BA, TEXAS A&M UNIVERSITY

Journalism 2002

COMMUNITY INVOLVEMENT

- Barkitecture Austin Web Developer, Silent Auction Chair
- Dress for Success Austin Administrative & Image Consultant
- Big Brothers Big Sisters Dallas Big Sister Volunteer

PROFESSIONAL CERTIFICATIONS & ORGANIZATIONS

- Certified Scrum Master (CSM)
- Certified Scrum Product Owner (CSPO)

TECHNICAL SKILLS & SOFTWARE SYSTEMS

- HTML, CSS
- JavaScript, React, Node, Redux
- SQL
- Atlassian Jira & Confluence
- InVision
- Looker
- Salesforce
- Google Analytics, MixPanel